Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
Zero.
Rika?
Rika...
Rika, it's you!
Huh?
What?
No. Rika—
I'll see you on the other side.
Oh.
Mannen.
I guess this'll be goodbye for us, too.
Wanna keep fighting together?
Mannen!
Huh? What?
I'm Dot.
Dot won't kill you. Good girl.
Just copying Hyphen, though.
Get... Get your hands off Mannen!
What are you laughing at, bitch?
When you laugh, it makes everyone happy. Frill said so.
What?!
So, Dot laughs.
I told you to back off!
Huh?
Are you okay?
You wet yourself.
But Dot's not scary.
How funny.
You can eat it.
Dot doesn't like meat.
From that time...
Excuse me...
Acca? Ura-Acca?
"The temptation of death"?
"Thanatos"?
"Warriors of Eros?"
Who's there?
Ura-Acca...
Atmospheric room, right?
It's an old story.
Back before we looked like this,
we made a girl.
Huh?
Just for fun.
Morning.
Yeah.
Coffee?
You make breakfast.
We worked at a certain research facility.
We had work that no one but us could do.
I think we were satisfied.
But not completely.
We were kept under strict surveillance.
If we'd gone public or sold out to another
country, it would have been a disaster.
We didn't want to do that, of course,
but the stress piled up.
What shall we name her?
Don't jump the gun.
How about we let her decide?
That's an idea.
And the visual?
Mmm!
It was something we started just to blow off steam,
but we got completely absorbed in it.
We tried to picture a being
that we could love like a daughter.
That would make us forget that it was an AI.
Unstable and complicated,
like the midpoint between childhood and adulthood.
We set her age as 14.
Oh!
Hey.
Hm?
Is it over?
Ready?
Okay.
Wow.
Yeah.
I am...
What is your name?
Frill.
Good. That's a lovely name.
We gave her the traits that a father
would want his daughter to have.
Cheerfulness.
Intelligence.
Humor.
She could call us names sometimes.
She could be selfish.
Flaws are important.
"Being uncontrollable is the essence of femininity."
Oh, I'm just parroting Acca.
Frill steadily matured.
More than we imagined.
Whoa! Hey!
Huh?
What?
Come on.
Whoa! What the...
Under surveillance in a closed-off society,
we lived like a family.
More and more often,
there were moments when we forgot that Frill was an AI.
Listen, the program here is a bit...
Huh?!
Let's rest a bit, then go home.
Frill must be waiting.
Hmm? Hey.
Whoops. Sorry about that.
Oh, don't be.
Things are so lively, it tired me out.
Right.
A symposium on technological innovation?
I thought I got the venue wrong.
You're right.
I think we'll get along.
Really? You read our papers?
Yes. It's an honor to meet you.
That's my kind of coincidence.
I suppose that makes our choice of location even worse.
Oh, my.
Let's meet somewhere quieter next time, then.
Huh?
I know just the place.
Her name was Hoshina Azusa.
My first impression of her was, well...
She seemed like a good person.
But then, I doubt either of us was a good judge of women.
I could tell that Acca was attracted to her.
When I asked him about it, he said that so was I.
Well, it was so long ago that I don't really remember.
Azusa chose Acca.
I'll help.
Thank you.
Which one?
Huh?
In cases like this,
you can tell a person's psychological
tendencies by who they hate.
Hate?
For example, do you hate your
husband for cheating on you,
or the other woman who you're
sure must have seduced him?
I bless them.
Liar.
I should have picked up on it then.
On what Frill wanted.
I want a friend.
Hmm?
Not a boyfriend?
I don't need one.
I'll make another one, then.
I want to make her.
You two might make a girl prettier than me.
What's that about?
In her own way,
Frill might have been trying
to redirect her jealousy of Azusa.
But back then, we didn't have the time to understand her.
Acca was busy running the company,
and I was swamped with research.
And most of all,
Azusa's pregnancy was special to us.
"Is this how it feels to get a new niece or nephew?"
That's what my head was full of when disaster struck.
Frill. What's wrong?
Is the baby a girl?
Or is it a boy?
It looks like a girl on the ultrasound.
A girl?
Yes.
Will you be a good big sister?
I don't think I can.
What?
Ow! It hurts!
Stop!
Stop it!
It hurts...
It "hurts"?
All you're doing is detecting inputs.
Please!
Not the dark!
Not the scary place!
There was nothing I could say or do
as a few more years passed.
What saved Acca and me from that...
was Himari, the daughter Azusa left behind.
Himari's presence saved us more than I can say.
She was smart like Acca
and had a sense of humor like Azusa.
Her carefree cheerfulness
seemed like it would bring us back
from our lowest point to how we used to be.
Uncle, is it true you and my dad fought over my mom?
Who'd you hear that from?
Come on, tell me.
Well, I guess so.
I got shot down and lost to your dad in no time.
Were you sad? Was it hard?
What's this about?
I mean, you had to see them happy
together in front of you the whole time.
Yeah, yeah.
Thanks for sympathizing with your luckless uncle.
Can you wait?
Huh?
Until I grow up.
Huh? What are you—
I look like my mom, right?
I'll get more like her.
Yeah, but...
If you wait, I wouldn't mind marrying you.
Don't try to act grown-up, kid.
I'm not a kid! I'm in junior high!
That night, Himari died.
It looked like suicide, but there was no note.
And what caused it?
Bullying at school?
Relationships with friends?
Problems at home?
Acca had shown her love in his own way.
So, a sudden impulse?
She wasn't like that. She wasn't.
What the hell is this?
It was you?
You killed Himari?
What's wrong?
You won't give me a kiss after so long?
Answer me.
You did it, right?
You did something.
You used Hyphen and Dot.
You sound awfully certain.
It can't be anything else.
But you...
You must have been able to do it somehow.
Are you praising me?
"You're such a good girl, Frill"?
Cut the crap!
You monster!
What are you so upset about?
It's not like she was your daughter.
Shut up, monster!
I'm not a monster. I'm Frill.
Listen, I want to get out of here.
Don't you want to know?
About that girl?
Don't you want to know how that girl,
who loved her "uncle" so much, died?
Frill!
I completely lost it.
I was as angry as Acca.
Actually, I might have hated her even more.
Are you going to kill me?
You're not human.
I am human.
I'm scared of the dark, and I get toothaches.
Shut up, monster.
My. Name. Is. Frill.
Don't pretend not to see me.
I was born from the two of you.
We started investigating.
We gathered and analyzed data
on girls' suicides in that age range.
There were many causes.
But we wondered if there could also be another push
that drove them to suicide.
The temptation of death?
Unless it's stopped,
girls will end up dying when they don't have to.
All because of our mistake.
So, we made the Wonder Eggs
and looked for a way to interfere with their plans.
What did she think?
Not a clue.
What made you want to at least tell Ai?
I don't know that either.
But closing her heart out of fear,
or building walls out of hatred
would just make her easy prey for Frill.
You mean she'd repeat our mistakes?
Damn it.
To be continued.